{
    "id": "29e7f32a462e4f4688086708d09a1526",
    "title": "Present or past participle worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a4adea4f2ccd41f78332b25eb09bcd15",
            "title": "Present or past participle quiz",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "………………. with milk and sugar, it makes a delicious breakfast.",
                    "description": "The complete sentence is 'When it is served with milk and sugar....'",
                    "answers": [
                        "Served",
                        "Serving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Most of the people ……………… to the party were neighbors.",
                    "description": "The complete sentence is 'Most of the people who were invited to the party...'",
                    "answers": [
                        "invited",
                        "inviting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Not ………………. what to do, I called the doctor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "knowing",
                        "known"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The people ...................... have been informed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "concerned",
                        "concerning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The professor is …………………. by his students.",
                    "description": "This is a passive construction and it is constructed with a past participle. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "admiring",
                        "admired"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was ………………….. by the way she spoke to me.",
                    "description": "We make passive constructions with past participles.",
                    "answers": [
                        "annoying",
                        "annoyed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I found her sitting at a table ……………… with papers.",
                    "description": "The complete sentence is 'I found her sitting at a table that was covered with papers'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "covering",
                        "covered"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was very ..................... by her performance.",
                    "description": "We make passive constructions with past participle forms.",
                    "answers": [
                        "amused",
                        "amusing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her performance was really ………………..",
                    "description": "Ing forms are used to make present and past continuous tense forms.",
                    "answers": [
                        "amusing",
                        "amused"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The first runner came in closely ………………….. by the second.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "following",
                        "followed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}